healwithfood.org 2017-05-29

# Privacy Policy | HealWithFood.org

By visiting HealWithFood.org (the "Site"), you (the "User") consent to the practices and policies outlined in this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy"). If you do not agree with the following policy in its entirety, please do not use this Site.

## Collection of Aggregate Data

A cookie (also known as a HTTP cookie) is a piece of code that a web site or its service providers may transfer to your browser. Cookies are used to capture and store certain data such as user preferences, geographical location of the user, previous activity, and other information. You can configure your web browser not to accept any cookies, but be aware that this may hinder the functionality of some websites.

HealWithFood.org may use cookies to collect general information about site traffic and User behavior. This information is used to analyze the effectiveness and popularity of this Site, and to improve the services and user experiences provided by this Site.

## Third-Party Advertising

In addition, third party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads based on the User's prior visits to this Site. Google's use of its DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to the User based on his or her visit to HealWithFood.org and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Google's [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences) or by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) (the latter can also be used to opt out of the use of other third-party vendors' cookies for interest-based advertising).

HealWithFood.org accepts no responsibility for the technologies, tools and practices of the third parties that provide advertising and related services on this Site. This Privacy Policy does not cover any collection, use, or disclosure of information by such third parties. The information gathering practices and privacy policies of such third parties are governed entirely by their own privacy statements, not this one.

## Links to Other Websites

This Site contains links to other websites which are not owned or operated by HealWithFood.org. HealWithFood.org does not have control over such websites, and is therefore not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you may provide while visiting such websites.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

HealWithFood.org reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to change, modify, or otherwise alter this Privacy Policy at any time. If the Policy is updated, the _Last Update_ date at the bottom of this page will be updated. Your continued use of the HealWithFood.org website following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy on this page means that you accept such changes. Your use of this website is entirely voluntary, and you may discontinue to use HealWithFood.org at any time.

## Any Questions?

If you have any queries or concerns about privacy on this Site, please contact HealWithFood.org via e-mail at info (at) healwithfood.org

**Last Update:** 05/05/2013
